You should coach him.
Are you sure?
Is it true
that your family and Sun's are betting
on the tennis match?
Who started this rumor?
Hey!
If you don’t feel better,
I’m not competing with you.
Is this you being a good sport again?
Hey, guys!
Are you guys all right?
Bay!
Sun!
-Bay, what’s wrong?
-Sun!
Bay!
Sun!
Sun, how are you feeling?
Hello, we have two unconscious boys
at Bangkok Pipat School.
-Sun!
-Bay!
Bay.
Bay, how are you?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Honey, go get the doctor.
You’re okay, right?
Mom, how about Sun?
Oh, you’re getting up?
Sun’s mother,
I’m so sorry.
Here, doctor.
Everyone,
please give me some spaceso I can do my job.
But, doctor, Bay has just woken up.
Come on, honey.
Let’s wait outside.
-Let him do his job.
-Please, everyone.
Come on.
I’ll be right back.
Yes.
Breathe in slowly.
Just rest for a while,
and you can go home.
Thank you, doctor.
Why are you hugging me?
Umm...
Umm, you’re up?
I’ll go get the doctor.
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION,MINISTRY OF CULTURE
-Hello.
-Hey.
Umm, how are the boys doing?
They’re resting.
But the doctor said they’ll be fine.
That’s good. Well...
Umm, the principal
wanted me to inform all of you
about...
the tryout for PREM’S GAME 31.
-Sun gets the spot?
-Bay gets the spot?
No, sir.
The principal said
she wouldn’t send anyone to join PREM’S GAME 31,
neither Sun nor Bay.
-Hey, why is that?!
-How could you say that, Kong?!
The principal also said,
Umm...
“Instead of seeing athletes compete with sportsmanship,
this has now turned into a ridiculous bet.”
That’s what she said.
Why didn’t she come to tell us herself?!
The principal is not available right now.
She also wanted me to tell you that
she hoped
both families
would void the contract
and never do anything like this again.
If you’ll excuse me.
Goodbye, everyone.
See what happened?
Now we’re screwed.
What contract?
Kong.
Huh?
What are you and the principal up to?
Nothing.
Well, we are.
But I can’t say anything right now.
When I can,
you’ll be the first to know.
Promise?
Promise.
Boy Boat!
Wow,
I haven’t seen you for ages.
When are you coming back to study?
How long are you going to take a breakfrom school?
It’s nothing.
I’ve just been busy these days.
I’ll catch you later.
Yeah?
Okay, see you later.
Yeah.
See you, man.
Come on.
Hold on,
you dropped out of school?
What happened?
You can tell me.
I’m here for you.
And I promise
I will not judge you.
But... who else knows about this?
Just my family.
I’m not that worried about it,
but my dad is.
Hmm.
Okay.
That’s fine.
If you don’t want to talk about it,
I understand.
And about what you were saying
to your friend,
I promise not to tell anyone.
Just don’t forget,
whenever you’re ready,
you can tell me.
I have to go.
See you later.
Kong!
When I’m ready,
you’ll be the first to know.
I promise.
Okay.
Thank you, Pa.
You just can’t help it, can you?
Well, that man...
He stole my dim sum recipe
and bullied our son.
You really don’t want me to fight back?
Stop using them as an excuse.
Whether it’s about him stealing
your recipe or what ever,
I don’t want to hear it.
When you’ve really lost everyone,
that’s when you’ll realize it, right?
Mom,
our ride’s here.
Honey,
did you see him at the hospital?
That boy was staring at our son without blinking.
He was trying to pick a fight,
wasn’t he?
Enough. Come on.
Go. Stop thinking about it.
Go.
So frustrating.
Are you sure you’re okay?
Yeah.
I’m not hurting,
just feeling a bit sore.
You’ve been unusually quiet.
You didn’t have a concussion, did you?
I’m just a bit upset.
Upset about what?
About Sun, of course.
Let me tell you.
Sun did it again.
Last time, his shoulder was hurting
This time he did it again.
He just doesn’t know his limits.
One day, he’ll drop dead on the court, just wait.
You’re worried about him?
What?!
I’m not worried.
I’m just annoyed.
If I win,
he’ll use this as an excuse.
Didn’t you and Sun use to be
best friends before?
Huh?
That was back then.
But now,
him and I,
we hate each other.
-Hate each other?
-Yeah.
Do you really hate each other,
or are you just pretending, huh?
(ADD TO YOUR STORY)
♪ I admit my heart has wanted you ♪
♪ Ever since the day I first met you ♪
(SAMING PHON FAI)
Why are you leaving so early?
Did you get a medical certificate yesterday?
Huh?
The medical certificate.
I did.
Let me see.
Why? Are you a doctor?
I’m not.
Just let me see.
(What the hell?)
Quickly.
That’s it.
Hey.
Did the teacher ask you to get it?
What did the doctor say?
I can’t read this.
He said not to overexert myself,
not to exercise too strenuously,
and...
there are no injuries anywhere on my body.
That’s good.
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
I’m not smiling.
You’re talking nonsense.
It’s good that you’re okay.
I’m off.
Hey, don’t you need the certificate anymore?
Nope!
Hey! What’s wrong with him?
My pen.
Hey!!
Sun, you’re back!
Oh, wow,
after yesterday’s match,
I thought you’d take a break for a month.
I know.
It was brutal.
Did I look that messed up yesterday?
Totally!
And...
Were you guys worried about me?
Of course, we were.
Why would you even ask that?
So worried that…
you wanted to give me a hug?
Huh?
What’d you say?
Let...let me put it like this.
If, after I woke up,
New Captionyou came over and hugged me,
why would you do that?
Because I was glad
and relieved.
Like, “Yay, Sun is okay!”
Oh, whatever.
You do that.
As for the hugging...
I’ll pass.
But I was worried about you.
What about…sitting next to me?
Like...waiting for me to wake up.
Would you do that?
Hmmm.
Don’t even.
Yesterday, after they carried you to
the hospital,
he was still asking us to go eat mala.
Hey! Ahem.
What’s wrong with you?
Were you really worried about me?
But at least
I would want to give you a hug.
Mmm.
Don’t lie to me.
Oww!
What the hell?
Why did you do that?
Bay!
What’s wrong with you?
I should be the one asking you that.
About the medical certificate this morning
and the fact that you hugged me at the hospital.
Why?
Is Zippo the only one allowed to hug you?
Don’t drag others into this.
Do you even realize
you’ve been acting super weird?
How?
Well, you...
you’ve been acting like you care about me.
Hey! What?
Maybe I knocked my head on the ground
and my brain got deprived of oxygen.
Bay!
What are you following me for?
Just answer me.
Why did you hug me?
I don’t know.
I wasn’t thinking.
I was just...
Just what?
Spit it out.
♪ I admit my heart has wanted you ♪
♪ Ever since the day I first met you ♪
The question you asked me,
I’d like to know the answer, too.
Oh,
you guys are here?
The principal wants to see you.
Both of you.
Yes, sir.
I have something to tell you.
We’ve thought this through carefully,
and we’ve decided that you two have to
compete in PREM’S GAME 31
in the men’s doubles event,
together.
-Huh?!
Yesterday, Coach Kong told me
he saw how you performed during the tryout.
When you two played, you had...
What is it? Chemistry, Coach Kong?
Chemistry?
It’s called tactics.
Yeah.
When you two play together,
you cover each other’s weaknesses really well.
If you’re on the same team,
you could be a very strong team.
That’s called chemistry.
Eh?
You said our school wasn’t going to
send any representatives, didn’t you?
Well, I had to say that
so your fathers would stop interfering.
Anyway, I still have to send representatives
to PREM’S GAME 31.
The principal and I have decided
that Zippo will play singles,
while you two will play doubles.
This way, you two might stop fighting.
But I have to ask you
not to tell your families just yet.
Urg,
even if I don’t tell him now,
he’ll find out anyway.
I’ll have to join the tournament,
go to practice,
and stuff.
-Right.
-I’ll have all of you
go to an out-of-town training camp together.
The whole tennis club.
-Huh? But...
-Out of town?
You can start training this evening.
Yes, ma’am.
Chop-chop.
Don’t forget to sign these.
Close the door behind you.
Now,
once you’ve finished running,
pair up and warm up.
Hey,
you’re going to play together.
You have to practice together
so you can sync up quickly.
It’s giving enemies-to-lovers trope.
Hey!
-Hey!
I already stepped out.
What the hell are you doing?
Yeah, yeah.
My bad.
One more time.
What’s wrong with these two?
Don’t move your knees.
Nice!
Support.
Nice.
-Yay!!
Why are you still hanging out with that family’s son, huh?
But I promised Bay
we would keep playing doubles together
until we make the national team.
If you keep this up,
I’ll send you off to live with your grandpa.
You and Bay are so in sync.
We used to play together as kids
before...
our families became rivals.
Is that true?
That’s why.
That’s why what?
It doesn’t look like you really hate each other.
Bay seems to really worry about you.
I don’t know.
I can’t keep up with his attitude.
One day he’s nice,
the next he’s mad at me again.
But during your match,
he was following your moves.
If he hated you, he wouldn’t support you that much.
I think he still sees you as his friend.
Trust me.
Actually, I’m kind of glad
that I get to play doubles with him again,
being on the same team.
If we compete and come back as champions,
it would be so satisfying for me.
Like, I wouldn’t want anything else in my life.
You’re gonna be champion!
Champion for sure.
You think so?
I know so.
I’ll get to go home by BTS today.
Oops, sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
Eh?
Where is he?
I’m here to withdraw.
But you did amazing today.
If you’re worried about your family...
In fact, it’s not about my family at all.
It’s me.
I don’t want to play with him.
Besides,
I don’t even want to play tennis again.
What the hell is your problem?
Come talk to me outside.
Hey, hey!
What the f*ck is wrong with you?
I just don’t want to play.
Would you stop being like this?
I’m tired of it.
You’re tired?
If that’s so, stop talking to me.
I really want to know.
Does getting to play doubles together again
not mean anything to you?
No.
Am I supposed to feel something?
I quit playing a long time ago.
And what happened back then
doesn’t mean a thing to me.
Besides,
who would want to play with you?
You f*cking suck.
Hey!
You’re crying?
Do you even care?
You’re always like this.
You come into my life
then you leave me.
How many times have you done that to me?
SAMING PHON FAI
I shouldn’t have let you back into my life.
Coach Kong,
I have something important to ask you.
I really want to know.
Do you really hate each other,
or are you just pretending, huh?
We do hate each other.
I think you’re just pretending to.
Why would you think that?
If you really hated each other,
no one would try to stop you from being with Sun.
You chose to act like this
because it might be the only way
you can have him in your life.
Am I right?
It’s not like that.
So, if Sun is not in your life anymore,
you will be happier, right?
You don’t have to answer me.
Just sleep on it
and find the answer for yourself.
Bay!
What is it, Coach?
Are you two fighting again?
It’s nothing new.
I fight with him every day.
Why are you so excited about it?
I’m not.
It’s just...
This time, Sun...
is dropping out of school.
Huh? Dropping out of school?
Mmm.
SAMING PHON FAI
Is there anything wrong?
You seem distracted.
It’s nothing.
I’m just...
thinking about school.
Coach Kong called to tell me about it.
About how you want to drop out of school
and take the equivalency exam later.
Is there something bothering you?
Do you want to tell me?
I don’t know if I’m the reason.
If I am, I’m sorry.
Pa,
this has nothing to do with you.
I’m just tired. That’s all.
If I'm part of the reason you're feeling tired,
I’m really sorry.
I’m sorry about the bet as well..
This is not about you at all.
I’m just tired. Really.
Let’s eat, Pa.
I’ll get you some rice.
Please eat a lot, Pa.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Coach Kong told me you’re dropping out.
What do you think you’re doing?
Isn’t that a bit dramatic?
I’m exhausted, Bay.
I’ll just leave.
Well, I won’t let you.
Why?
Why? I don’t know.
But I won’t let you go.
My dad doesn’t even stop me.
Who are you?
Damn it, Sun.
I’ve made up my mind.
I’m going to take the equivalency exam later.
For now, I’m moving into a dorm near
the athletes’ training camp.
You should be glad
you won’t have to see me anymore.
If I told you the truth,
would you change your mind?
What truth?
The truth about why I left you.
SAMING PHON FAI
(It all started)
GET READY FOR THE MERLION DIM SUM RECIPE EVERYONE HAS BEEN LOOKING FOR
(When my dad decided to open a dim sum shop like your dad did.)
What do you think you’re doing, Bee?!
I’m building my shop.
What shop?!
It’s my own restaurant.
This is a dim sum shop just like mine!!
(Then everything just...)
(got out of hand.)
Why are you still hanging out with that family’s son, huh?
I told you
one day he will betray you too.
But I promised Bay
we would keep playing doubles together
until we make the national team.
Look, Sun,
you can get a new partner.
No, I want to play with Bay.
If you keep this up,
I’ll send you off to live with your grandpa.
-(We used to play together)
-You’ll have to study at another school.
You won’t get to play tennis anymore.
(but then...)
(we had to go our separate ways.)
I’m not playing tennis with you anymore.
(I was secretly hoping)
(if one day)
(our fathers could work through their problems,)
(we might get to play tennis together again.)
(But as time went by,)
(I slowly started to let go of that hope.)
(I thought being apart would be for the best.)
POSTS.
(But when someone else actually took my place,)
(I couldn’t handle it.)
BLOCK.
BLOCK S.SUNN_YT?
Next match, okay?
-Okay.
-Let’s try again.
-What the...?
-Hey!
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
(Before,)
(I didn’t know what my feelings were.)
What’s your f*cking problem, Bay?
What?
What are you gonna do?
When will you stop?
Why do you want me to hate you so much?
(I just thought...)
Huh?
You think you can hate me, right?
(it was hate.)
I f*cking hate you, too.
(I thought the two of us)
(could never be the same again.)
I feel like I would go crazy
every time you leave me.
So you...
choose to leave me instead?
I’m so afraid.
I’m afraid that...
if we love each other,
someone will take you away from me some day.
I just want you in my life.
Even if we have to be enemies,
I can take it.
I really, really like you, Sun.
I’m sorry
it took me this long to realize.
But after hearing this,
will you still disappear?
When you said you love me,
what kind of love was it?
♪ I admit my heart has wanted you ♪
♪ Ever since the day I first met you ♪
♪ You filled the missing space beside me ♪
♪ Now everything means more than it used to be ♪
2 YEARS AGO
Ouch!
Damn.
What the hell do you think you’re doing?
Stop pulling pranks on my partners.
No one wants to play tennis with me now.
Serves you right.
You’re trying to ruin my future?
Huh?
Mmm.
Oww! Damn it.
If no one’s playing doubles with you,
go play singles instead.
Don’t be dumb.
Your dad is dumb.
Hey.
Why?
You can win on your own?
You’re afraid you’ll lose?
Are you a loser?
Huh? Loser.
-You suck.
-Shut the hell up!
-Assh*le! Don’t run away.
-Loser.
-Get back here.
-Come on.
-Stop running away then.
You can’t catch me.
Ha, loser.
Ha,
loser, loser, loser.
Oh, sht.
Can you just play singles from now on
for me?
(What’s wrong?)
(Why are you here alone?)
(What’s going on with you?)
(You’ve been avoiding me all day.)
(Well, I don’t know how to act.)
(I don’t even know how I feel.)
(Do you like me, Sun?)
(If you like me too,)
(I’m willing to get through any obstacle.)
(It feels great knowing that you like me.)
(But does this mean I like you too?)
(I’m still not sure.)
(Will you let me try to win you over)
(until you’re sure about your feelings?)
♪ I admit my heart has wanted you ♪
♪ Ever since the day I first met you ♪
♪ You filled the missing space beside me ♪
(Just trust me.)
(I will always support you.)
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION, MINISTRY OF CULTURE